(Bernadette:)Yeah. Or you'd be
the oldest one here.
(Penny:)Really? Is that how you
talk to your mother?
(Howard:)He just parked.
He's on his way up.
(Leonard:)Good. This is exciting.
(Raj:)It is. I feel alive.
What if we do get caught?
Who cares?
(Leonard:)So we get banned from Comic-Con.
(Raj:)Maybe slapped with a fine.
I'll be an astronaut and a bad boy.
(Howard:)How will women keep their pants on?
(Raj:)Maybe it'll come up when
I apply for citizenship.
(Raj:)Oh, crap, what if it comes up
when I apply for citizenship?
(Leonard:)I wonder if we'd have
to disclose something like this
(Leonard:)when we apply for grants.
(Raj:)He's gonna be here any second,
what should we do?
(Howard:)You guys are such babies.
(Howard:)I'll handle this.
(Howard:)If he thinks we're not home,
he'll go away.
(Raj:)I thought you were a badass.
(Howard:)I lied about the Pepto,
I always use the little cup!